Strong because
therma and some stocks like Reliance are getting
good traction right now,
though Nifty is indicating that we wo
n't call it a slight gap down, we will
start with a hockey-like downtick, we will start flex,
let's start flat due to the mother, on
Tuesday the opposition will be seen
joining Delhi with its excellent tax
line, then that Irshad,
good morning Ashish, what is it, today you people have given
this line yourself,
ours, you have to move, HDFC Bank,
you have to move and IM data has
hit SBI, hanging from Venus,
you have to move, HDFC Bank, you have to move,
Ashish, today two midcap
largest midcap stocks, so both are Fundo
stocks and we will start first with ICC
Lombard, ICC GI whose symbol is
on NSC, first of all let's take a chart
of ICC Lombard and let's see what kind of
pattern is being formed here, see, this is
your ICC Lombard pattern and in
this, okay, first show the graphic in the full frame, I
think the last date has passed, okay, well
and so first
show the chart once in the full frame, after that  I was
discussing here. The last time the
stock came, it broke out of the channel, then it went
down and took a second atom. And this
time we are preparing to hold it
above the channel, so this is a positive
for ICC Lombard. Now, as
we were showing that understanding, clearly a price
pattern is a little positive
for ICC Lombard here. And
if you look at the fundamentals, then
obviously its premium has also been
quite good. So for this, let's move on to the
next
stock. The graphic is not there. Our next stock is I
Bill Stop. This is done.
Similarly, let's
bring the chart of Lambesis Ampere
and see how Emphasis
is behaving. This is the chart of Emphasis on the
screen in front of you. Look, it is
preparing to come out of a channel. It is a 16-month
channel. It is preparing to come out of it.
Similarly, there is a slight rise in IT these days. There has
also been delivery shortcut bing.
Standard disclaimer:
These two stocks are not ICC.  Lombard and
again both these stocks are kept
Veero Pari opening tick tock what is happening
brother
yes